Guide to the Robert E. Butts Papers, 1908-1997 ASP.2000.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Multimedia, 1972-1997; III.; 32 Document Boxes
  - Side A Sensitive Dictations, Letters of Rec, also Some Personal Corr, Pro. Conf (CPA) (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 1)
  - WTC Music (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 2)
  - Side A Dictated Corresp. For Phil. Of Sci. c.1987 (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 3)
  - Side A Dictation or Message Directed at University Colleagues RE: Conferences, Budgets, Committees c.1972-3 (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 4)
  - Radio Show Called 'Talk Show', Topic is Witched and Witchcraft, Dr. Butts is a Guest on the Show (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 5)
  - Robert E. Butts: Message for Students in Phil 145 (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 6)
  - Witches, Dr. Butts Is A Guest On a Radio Show The Segment He Appears On Is About the History of Witches, Witchcraft (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 7)
  - 'Talk Radio' Continued, Dr. Butts Is Guest and They Are Ending His Visit to the Show (Box 28, Folder 1, Cassette 8)
- Oversized Materials, 1947-1994; IV.
  This series consists of oversized materials that have been separated from the collection proper for storage purposes. It contains a small number of documents, most of which are diplomas and certificates that are biographical in nature. The first document, the certificate from the Weigh-House at Oudewater, is from a historical site in the Netherlands where accused witches were weighed and certified as non-witches during medieval witch hunts, a subject of research interest in Butts' later life.
  - Testimony of the Art of Weighing in the Weigh-House at Oudewater, the Netherlands, 1994 (Box 29, Item 1)
  - Delta Phi Alpha National Honorary German Fraternity, Syracuse University, 1951 (Box 29, Item 2)
  - Alexander von Humboldt-Sitfung Award, 1992 (Box 29, Item 3)
  - Diploma of Robert Earl Butts, Philosophiae Doctoris, University of Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 29, Item 4)
  - Manheim Township High School Diploma, 1947 (Box 29, Item 5)